Elcin Koyuncu

(863) 722-4573 | <u>elcinkoyuncu@gmail.com</u> | Fort Lauderdale, FL, 33309 <u>linkedin.com/in/elcin-koyuncu-us</u> | github.com/ElcinKoyuncu | https://elcinkoyuncu.github.io/Portfolio/

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Solution-driven Full Stack Web Developer with 8 years of analytical experience; proven management, sales and coaching skills. Recognized for innovation, being detail oriented, working under pressure and adapting new conditions. Excellent interpersonal communication skills and collaborator who works well on team-based projects as well as independently. Recognized for proven complex problem-solving abilities to contribute effectively as a part of a fast-paced, quality-driven team.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Node.Js., Express, JavaScript, jQuery, Jest, Selenium, JSX, GIT, GitHub, MongoDB, MySQL, Mongoose, HTML5, CSS3, Bootstrap, APIs, Heroku, Terminal, AJAX, Restful API, ES6, React Hooks, JSON, Sequelize, Adobe

Dreamweaver, Adobe Illustrator, Adobe Photoshop, Adobe InDesign, CorelDRAW, Fortran77, Task/Jira, Microsoft Office.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Sunelli; Florida 11/2019- Present

Graphic Designer

Designing signs for the stores

• Design signs for every season.

Uptown Cheapskate; Fort Lauderdale, FL 04/2021 **Supervisor** 11/2018 -

- Created timely and accurate inventory, cash, and production reports for senior managers.
- Coordinated merchandising of new products, including displays, signage, and sales enablement.
- Processed exchanges, refunds, and team member purchases to keep cashiers focused on efficiently checking out regular customers.
- Kept merchandise fresh by monitoring use of proper stock rotation procedures and setting up promotions to move out aging products.
- Evaluated data on stock levels, customer sales and other factors, assessed trends and reported on findings to help senior management make effective operational decisions.
- Trained new employees to get ready to work in the store.

Iyi Fikir LLC.; Adana, TURKEY 03 /2013 - 01/2018 Owner

- Developed creative design for marketing packages, including print materials, brochures, banners, and signs
- Developed collateral such as display, marketing, and packaging materials to support product branding strategies.
- Created and updated trend boards investigated changing conditions and recommended strategic adoptions to capitalize on projected changes.
- Pursued business development opportunities and fostered positive relationships with clients through engaging presentations.

EDUCATION

Full Stack Web Development Certificate - University of Miami ; Miami, FL | **2021-Present** *A* 24-week intensive boot camp program focused on gaining technical programming and market-driven skills.

Pedagogical Proficiency Certificate - Cukurova University;

Adana, Turkey | 2007 BS Degree in Physics - Cukurova

University; Adana, Turkey

Web and Graphic Design Certificate - Bilge Adam Academy | 2012